{
    "id": "c361c9d0288d482e86aaad452a2d5c15",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise | Confusing Words",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "86bd61e645614536ab196b0468e165c9",
            "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He was so angry the ………………………. stood out on his forehead.",
                    "description": "Vein means blood vessel. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "vains",
                        "veins",
                        "vanes"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rescuers made a ……………………. attempt to reach the sinking boat.",
                    "description": "Vain means futile or useless.",
                    "answers": [
                        "vein",
                        "vain",
                        "vane"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The ………………………… politician had no thought of the public welfare.",
                    "description": "Venal means corrupt.",
                    "answers": [
                        "venal",
                        "venial"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "His new ………………………….. doesn’t fit well.",
                    "description": "A suit is a coat with matching trousers or shirt.",
                    "answers": [
                        "suit",
                        "suite",
                        "soot"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Reserve the bridal ……………………….. at the hotel.",
                    "description": "A suite is a set of related rooms.",
                    "answers": [
                        "soot",
                        "suit",
                        "suite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He spoke to the audience in a humorous ………………………",
                    "description": "A vane is a direction pointer. Vein can mean mood.",
                    "answers": [
                        "vain",
                        "vein",
                        "vane"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A …………………….. sin does not keep one out of Heaven.",
                    "description": "Venial means pardonable.",
                    "answers": [
                        "venial",
                        "venal"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Waterloo is a ……………………….. battleground.",
                    "description": "Historic means famous in history.",
                    "answers": [
                        "historic",
                        "historical"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is a …………………………. fact that George Washington had false teeth made of wood.",
                    "description": "Historical means concerned with history, recorded or chronicled. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "historic",
                        "historical"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is very ………………………… about her appearance.",
                    "description": "Vain means proud, too concerned or arrogant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "vain",
                        "vein",
                        "vane"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A ………………………. of food was found in the cave.",
                    "description": "A hoard means a stockpile. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "hoard",
                        "horde"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A ………………………… of Tatars invaded Europe.",
                    "description": "Horde means a crowd.",
                    "answers": [
                        "horde",
                        "hoard"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}